sportsbun.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy - Sportsbun

We at Sportsbun.com sincerely respect your privacy. Please read the following information to learn more about our policy.

**The Policy** :

Our privacy policy explains how Sportsbun.com treats personal information, such as your name, address, e-mail, and phone number, which we collect and receive that may otherwise not be public knowledge. This includes information related to your historical use of our site.

**Information Collection** :

Sportsbun.com will collect personal information when you sign up for our newsletter via our registration process. Most other sites require this as well. We will ask for your name, e-mail address. When you register and sign-in, you are no longer anonymous to us, you are our friend.

We receive and record information from your computer and browser, including IP address, cookie information, software and hardware, and any pages you visit on our site.

We use this information for the following purposes to:

  * Customize the content and advertising you see,
  * Improve our services in terms of convenience and entertainment value,
  * Contact you,
  * Conduct research and,
  * Provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

**Information Sharing** :

Sportsbun.com will not share, sell, or rent your personal information with other parties except to provide services you have asked for and only with your permission.

We may display targeted advertising based on personal information. We do not provide personal information to the advertiser when you interact with ads. However, advertisers may assume that people who interact with targeted ads meet their targeting criteria. (i.e., men 18-29 from the US).

**Cookies** :

Sportsbun.com may set and access cookies* on your computer.

*A cookie allows a website to recognize you after your initial visit. It saves general information, and is useful when returning to websites you have previously registered with.

We may let other companies that advertise on our site set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies use of cookies will be subject to their own privacy policies, not ours. Other companies do not have access to Sportsbun.com’s cookies.

Confidentiality and Security access to your personal information is limited to employees who need to come in contact with you, to provide services to you; or to do their jobs.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy** :

We reserve the right to update this policy without prior notice of any kind. You will receive notification regarding significant changes to your registered e-mail address or by notice on the site.
